刚开始我们寄予了厚望
We started with such high hopes.
因为前几任老板都死了
With all the previous owners being dead,
旅馆现在由我们管理了
the hotel was under new management... ours.
我们决定按照我们的想法
We were determined to remake the Cortez
改造Cortez
in our own image.
这里不仅仅是家旅馆
This would be no mere hotel.
我们本想成为无依无靠者的家人
We had ambitions to be a family to the friendless,
给遭受冷落的人带去安慰
a comfort to those in the cold,
建造一个包容的蜂巢
a beehive of acceptance.
本该是个完美的结局
It was supposed to be the perfect ending.
- 你们好 - 你好
- Oh, hello. - Hello.
欢迎下榻Cortez
Welcome to the Cortez.
请在宾客登记簿上签名
Please, sign our guest book.
好的
Sure.
你们要来杯香槟吗
May I offer the two of you a glass of champagne?
行啊
Don't mind if I do.
我觉得他们是"冒险旅行家"网站
I think those are the reviewers
来的评论人
from that Internet site, Trip Adventurers.
他们定是听说我们旅馆盛大重开的消息了
They must've heard about our grand reopening.
我知道
I know.
没看到我这满脸堆积着
Can't you see the ridiculously gracious smile
亲切地有些荒唐的微笑吗
plastered on my face?
这股刺激气味是怎么回事
What is that pungent odor?
是鼠尾草 用来净化灵魂的
Sage. To cleanse the spirit.
我带你们去房间
I'll show you to your room.
给Cortez这块宝石润色
To polish the jewel that is the Cortez,
不仅需要钱 这个我们从卖掉女伯爵
it required not only money... which we got from liquidating
那无数艺术品得到了
the Countess's numerous pieces of art...
不过还得在网上得到四星好评才行
it was going to take four stars on the Internet.
于是 我们说干就干
And so, we were off.
我们还没完成每层楼的装修 但这间是
We haven't finished with every floor, but this is one of
新装修的其中之一
our newly refreshed rooms.
埃及棉
Egyptian cotton.
四百线程的
400 thread count.
还有小酒吧
Minibar?
混合酒免费
Mixers are on the house.
如果还有其他需要
If there's anything else you need,
打电话就行
just pick up the phone.
谢谢
Thank you.
住得开心
Enjoy your stay.
你之前还想给个勉强及格
And you were ready to give it a pass.
咬我啊
Kill me.
逗我的吧
Are you kidding?
这可是东陶牌的双抽水马桶啊 亲
That's a Toto Neorest 700H, baby.
日本产的自动清洗神奇马桶
The Japanese self-cleaning wonder toilet.
我一直想试下这些东西呢
I have always wanted to try one of these.
这马桶没让你想拉一泡吗
Doesn't it just make you want to take a dump?
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
不得不说 房间不错
I got to say, it's a nice room.
他们花了血本 把能换的都换了
They spent every penny they had to change everything they could.
把床垫 特别是那些我划破的
They took out the mattresses,
给换了
especially the ones I split open.
还有那些浸泡在尿和血中
Took out the carpets,
多年的地毯
soaked through with so many years
也给换了
of piss and blood.
甚至家具都换了
They even changed the furniture.
但你们知道他们换不了的是什么吗
But you know what they couldn't take out?
是痛苦
The pain.
因为我还在这
'Cause I'm still here.
行了 我要请你离开
All right, I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
现在就走
Now.
天啊
Oh! God!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
快报警
Call the police!
有个疯婆子刚杀了我的搭档
Some crazy bitch just killed my partner!
求...
Please... ah!
天啊
Oh, my God. Oh!
Oh, God.
请你帮帮我
Please, you got to help me!
不 是你得帮我
No, no. You have to help me.
我是这杀人游戏中的新手呢
I'm new at this murder game,
天啊 太刺激了
and, Jesus Christ, is it a thrill.
对了
Ah, crap.
走廊尽头还有一个
We got another one down at the end of the hallway.
该死
Damn it.
不能再继续了
This has got to stop.
新地毯被他污染了
He stained the new carpet.
是啊 我们麻烦大了
Yeah, we got a serious problem.
鬼一直在杀客人
The ghosts keep killing the guests,
这样下去一星都休想得到
we're gonna end up with zero stars.
是时候开个会了
It's time we had a goddamn meeting.
大家好 欢迎
Hello! Welcome!
- 感谢你们出席 - 打扰一下
- Thank you all for coming. - Excuse me.
据我所知 现在是你俩管事了吧
My understanding is that you two are in charge now,
我想跟你谈谈换房间的事
and I'd like to speak to you about changing my room.
亲爱的 你都是鬼了
Sweetheart, you're a ghost.
想住哪间 就住哪间
You can choose whatever room you'd like.
没错 但问题是
Well, yes, but the problem is,
我挑好房间
after I pick a room
把我的色情小说搬进去后
and then settle in with my erotica novels,
我哪知道什么时候会有客人住进来
I never know if a guest is going to check in
打扰我
and disturb me.
我知道这里是洛杉矶
I know this is Los Angeles,
但我是个保守的姑娘 喜欢隐私
but I'm an old-fashioned girl and I like my privacy.
我觉得客人来的时候
I dig it when the guests come in.
就像一场免费黄片
It's like a free dirty movie.
我喜欢素人的自拍作品
I'm into that amateur stuff.
你们仨 玩真的了么
Are you three, like, a thing now?
对啊
Ya.
我们想泡伐木工
We try dating the lumberjack,
但他是同性恋
but he's a gay.
好了 大家 请听我说
Okay, everyone, please, listen.
事关紧要
This is important,
会影响你们每个人
and it affects every single one of you.
我们希望你们别再杀客人了
We would like you to stop killing the guests.
也不是你们所有人
It's not all of you,
我们想
but we are trying
在这建造些特别的东西
to build something special here.
一个真正的终点
A real... destination.
Carson要来两支橄榄球队
Look, they're gonna get two football teams down in Carson.
顺着110公路就二十分钟的路
That's 20 minutes down the 110.
这里或许能客满
This place could be filled.
但要是走漏了风声 来这住的人
But if it gets out that people are
会消失不见
checking in and disappearing,
这样明显不利于生意
then obviously, that's bad for business.
得了吧 Iris
Screw you, Iris.
你才是杀人最多的刽子手
You're the biggest killer in this room,
- 你这嗜血的恶魔 - 那是以前的我
- you bloodsucker. - Maybe in the past.
我现在喝得每一滴血都是捐赠得来的
But every drop of blood I drink now is donated.
这旅馆里被杀的人
Any murders that go on in this hotel
都是你们这类人干的
are done by your kind.
打断一下
Excuse me, but...
你说"我们这类人"是什么意思
what do you mean by "Our kind"?
别拐弯抹角了
Can we all just call
直说Will和我不就得了
a spade a spade and say you're talking about Will and I?
Woo忙着
I mean, Woo is
泡瑞典妞
too busy munching on Swedish fish
没空打扰他人
to bother anyone.
Marcy整天不是调戏自己
Marcy molests herself
就是抱怨个不停
or complains all day.
伐木工嘛 一副百无聊赖的样子
The lumberjack just mopes.
还有那对时髦情侣 游来荡去
And that hipster couple just trips around
整天因为甘蓝发牢骚
moaning about for kale.
只有Will和我
Will and I are the only ones
还在搞恶作剧寻找刺激
who still get off on a little bit of true mischief.
我们不会罢手的
And we're not stopping.
干掉一个
Ending some jerk-off
浪费空气的蠢货
who wastes the air that he breathes?
才是真正的乐趣
That is the real high.
我虽已死 但从没活得如此真实
I'm dead, but I've never felt more alive.
说得好
Beautifully said.
我完全同意
And I couldn't agree more.
但这件事上 我必须站在Cleopatra和
But I must come down on the side of Cleopatra
她朋友这边
and her friend on this issue.
算了吧
Oh, come on!
你跟我们说停止杀人
You telling people to stop killing
就像桑德斯上校告诉我们别吃鸡一样
is like Colonel Sanders telling us to stop eating chicken.
我不是很熟悉你的军人朋友
I'm not familiar with your military friend
和他对家禽的喜爱
and his fondness for poultry,
但我要停止杀戮了
but my killing days are over.
我以为十宗罪杀人
I thought the Ten Commandment killings
是我作品的开始
were the beginning of my work,
但事实证明是尾声
but it turns out that they are the epilogue.
后继有人 而我感到了圆满
The torch has been passed, and I feel complete.
这是明智的决定 而不是感性的抉择
But this is a practical decision, not an emotional one.
这是我们的家
This is our home.
坦白说 这是我们唯一的东西了
Frankly, it's the only one we've got.
如果没了这里 没人知道在这
None of us know what is waiting for us
以外的世界有什么等着我们
beyond this place if it no longer stands.
或许 没有这些墙的保护 我们会被
Perhaps, without these walls to protect us, we would all be
逼着去面对
forced to move on and face
造物主的审判
the judgment of our Maker.
如果我们不能维持生意 那就没赌注了
If we can't stay in business, all bets are off.
我们必须要出售
We'll have to sell.
或被驱逐
Or get evicted.
放屁
That's bullshit.
我为这里出了钱
I paid cash for this place.
我的律师会一直付保养费和税
My lawyers will keep paying the upkeep and the taxes
只要他们还有基金
for as long as they have the funds.
是啊 但不会维持太久 牛仔
Yeah, well, that's not gonna take very long, cowboy.
当然 你的生意值不少钱
Sure, your business was worth a fortune
在你活着的时候
when you were alive.
但你太自恋了
But you're such a narcissist
从未让别人插手过你的设计
that you never brought anyone else in to design your lines.
当你消失了 他们啥都没了
And when you disappeared, they had zilch.
现在一切都没了
Now the whole shithouse has gone up in flames.
你的股票一文不值了
Your stock is worth pennies.
你胡说
That is bullshit!
你个大骗子
You're a goddamn liar.
够了 这不是民主辩论
Enough! This is not a democracy!
我们不是在上议院
We are not in the House of Lords!
我们是一条船上的蚂蚱
We are a ship at sea!
说到你们这些幽灵 我才是队长
And when it comes to you spirits, I am captain!
听着 伙计们
So listen up, mateys!
美国内政部
There are six criteria
有六个准则
that the U.S. Department of Interior uses to determine
去判定一个地方是否值得
if a place is worthy of being called
称为历史地标
an historical landmark.
这个酒店符合那些标准
This hotel fits them all.
只有一项还未达成的是时间
The one thing it does not yet possess is time.
年代
Age.
2026年八月二十三日
August 23, 2026.
这所酒店就有一百年的历史了
That will make it 100 years that this hotel has stood.
到那天 它就会赢得应有的荣誉
And on that day, it will earn its rightful distinction
一个历史地标建筑
as an historical landmark.
他们就没法再拆掉这了
They won't be able to tear it down
就算他们想拆
even if they wanted to.
杀戮必须停止
The killing must stop!
该死的不
Oh, hell no.
我们中的一些人没法去
Some of us can't go out into the world
外面找同伴
to find companionship,
我不会停止收集灵魂
so I'm not gonna stop collecting souls
- 直到找到我的精神伴侣 - Sally 我不想
- until I find my soul mate. - Sally, I don't want
凶你 但你和我都明白
to get rough with you, but you and I both know
有让你去找伴侣的方法
there is a way to get you to do as I please.
还是 你不记得上次你不听我话的事了
Or do you not recall the last time you disobeyed me?
那就这么定了
So, it's settled, then.
死去的要点不就是没规则吗
The point of being dead is that there are no rules.
那是唯一的救赎
It's the only salvation.
谁在乎他们要拆掉这地方
Who gives a shit if they tear this place down
直接送我们下地狱
and send us all straight to hell?
还有什么更糟糕的事吗
It can't be any worse!
滚开
Go away!
一瓶赠送给我们
Complimentary bottle of champagne
永久贵宾居民的香槟
for our VIP long-term residents.
就是你 小姐
That's you, missy.
你省省吧
Save your breath.
我懂你的意思
I know what you're up to.
你的圣歌计谋 或许对别人有用
Your Kumbaya intrigues might work with the others;
但我不吃你这套
they're not gonna work with me.
很好
Good.
我们废话少说
We can cut the crap.
老天 你真是个孤独 悲惨的婊子
Jesus, you're one lonely, miserable bitch.
这才是你啊
Oh, there she is.
现在滚出我的房间
Now get the hell out of my room.
你这么苦大仇深的不累吗
Don't you ever get tired of being so goddamn bitter?
我想帮助你 Sally
I want to help you, Sally.
这话是推我坠楼的女人说的
This coming from the woman who shoved me out of a window.
好吧
Okay.
那事怪我
That's on me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的
Truly.
但 我们都不该沉浸在过去里
But it's no good for either of us to dwell in the past.
说实话 自从John走了 你就变了
Honey, you haven't been the same since John left.
当心啊 Iris
Watch it, Iris.
我还是可以把冰锥插入你的喉咙 任何时候
I can still take an ice pick to your throat, anytime.
你爱他
You loved him.
用你唯一知道的方式
The only way you knew how.
但他背弃了你
He turned his back on you,
在你为他做那么多之后
after all you'd done for him.
我懂那种感觉
I know how that feels.
你他妈一点也不知道我的感受
You don't know a damn thing about how I feel.
我的痛苦
About my pain.
唯一能消除烦恼的是
The only thing that takes the edge off
当我拉着人和我一起
is when I can pull people under with me.
让他们感受一盎司我的感受
Make them feel one ounce of what I feel.
之后我就不孤独了
Then I'm not alone.
但你看到了吗
But don't you see?
那些被你杀掉的人
All those people you've been killing, it's...
他们只是创口贴
they're just Band-Aids.
我还知道一个永久修复的方法
What if I knew of a more permanent fix?
你可以有长效的东西
You could have something long-lasting.
一个未来
A future.
什么未来
What future?
我死啦
I'm dead.
你生活在1994年的世界里
You've been living in a 1994 world.
时代变了
Times have changed.
Cortez自豪的向每个房间提供免费网络
The Cortez is proud to offer free Wi-Fi now in every room.
这是你去冒险的票子
Here's your ticket to adventure.
快点 打开它
Go on, open it.
我能用这个干嘛
What am I supposed to do with this?
我们无法改变过去
We can't change the past,
但你可以选择向前看 生活下去
but you can choose to move forward and live.
那又如何
So what?
我要变成机器里的鬼魂吗
I-I'm gonna be the ghost in the machine?
这正是你要做的
That's exactly what you're gonna be.
好了 看
Okay, look.
我帮你安装了
I loaded it up for you
推特 图享
with Twitter, Instagram,
脸书 你不用出门
Facebook. You don't need to be
也可以成为世界的一部分
out in the world to be a part of it.
在现代社会 没人会孤独
In the modern age, no one ever has to be alone.
一秒钟都不会
Even for a second.
全世界都在等你拥抱它呢 Sally
There's a whole world out there waiting to embrace you, Sally.
快点 你只需要沉浸在其中
Come on, all you have to do is dive in.
Sally离不开互联网了 就像水里的鱼
Sally took to the interwebs like a fish to water.
她做任何事
It was as if everything she did
只要拍出来
shot out a pulse of electricity.
世界的各个角落
And from all the corners of the globe,
人们都会回复
people responded.
陆陆续续 还要更多
In droves, tingling for more.
被吸引的观众打开双臂欢迎她
A rapt audience welcoming her with open arms,
急切的关注 等待她的每个字
desperate to connect, hanging onto her every word.
突然灰姑娘变成了白天鹅
Suddenly the girl no one wanted became the belle of the ball.
她可以说任何事 释放她的灵魂
She could say anything, bare her soul.
她孤独的声音 编织成了网络亚文化
Her lone voice weaving into its own cyber subculture.
安全的港湾
A safe harbor.
# 当你渴望 那就倾诉 #
It spits you out when you desire
# 征服 让你感到更高 #
Conquer...  it to feel you're higher...
在她沉醉在无限的崇拜中时
As she basked in sublime adoration,
对世界的麻木最终失去了吸引力
being numb to the world finally lost its appeal.
再一杯吗
Another?
我死了多久了
How long have I been dead?
一年多了吧
It's over a year now.
你觉得有多长呢
How long does it feel like?
向我没存在过一样
Like I don't exist.
所以你才开始因发泄而杀人吗
Is that why you've been acting out and killing those people?
我不知道我的公司倒闭了
I had no idea that my business was dead.
还没倒闭 不过也快了
Oh, it's not dead. It's dying.
他们准备怎么处置
Well, what have they done with it?
改成工厂吗
Factories?
第五大道上的精品商店吗
The stores on Rodeo, Fifth Avenue?
他们把时装部给关了
Well, they shuttered the couture division.
留着香水部和太阳镜部来维持运营
The perfumes and sunglasses are keeping everything else afloat.
你确实对这个世界很重要 知道吗
And you do matter in the world, you know.
只要事业在发展 你的儿子还茁壮成长着 你就不会被遗忘
As long as it lives and your son thrives, you matter.
我很感激你为他所做的一切
I'm grateful for what you've done for him.
撒切尔中学是我国最好的学校之一
Thatcher is one of the best schools in the country,
奥海镇一年四季气候宜人
and Ojai is year-round divine.
你该让他回来见见你的
You should let him come and visit you.
不了 不了
No. No.
这里不是年轻人该来的地方
This is no place for a young man.
这里到处弥漫着死亡的气息
All of the death here.
我不想他的纯真被这里污染
I don't want him to be poisoned by it.
就算无法见到他 我会有多心痛
Even if it breaks my heart that I can't see him.
我给你个建议吧
May I make a proposition?
你很美 但你不是我喜欢的类型
You're beautiful, but you're not my type.
没有经历过那种刻骨铭心的痛
The trapped spirits in this place
却受困于这里的鬼魂们 他们懂得
who aren't in perpetual misery understand that
如果你想要感受魔法的原理和功效
if you want to feel the magic of cause and effect,
你必须得要有个目标
you have to have a purpose.
你的时装店很出色
Your fashion house was iconic.
你也很出色
You're iconic.
早在在我"消失"之前
My fashion house was headed for disaster
我的时装店就已经经营惨淡了
long before I "Disappeared."
十年来我都没想到过一个原创的理念
I haven't had an original thought in a decade.
这里可是加利福尼亚啊
This is California!
涅重生之地啊
The land of reinvention.
我是说
I mean,
看看这里成就了怎样的我
look what this place did for me.
人们会认为我去了哪里呢
Where does everyone even think I am?
谣言比比皆是
Rumors abound.
去了戒毒所 精神病院 大病一场
Rehab, madness, illness.
只有过之 而无不及
Each one more scandalous than the last.
坦白说 流言蜚语就是这样
Frankly, it's marvelous publicity.
人们热衷于神秘的事物
People love a mystery.
构思吧
Sketch.
定个计划
Create.
再次融入进这个世界吧
Be part of the world again.
经营时装店可不止是画个草图这么简单
Running a fashion house is more than sketching.
比其他任何生意都难做 我需要模特
More than any other business, a line needs a face.
好吧
Okay.
没死之前 我做过售货员
I was a salesman in another life.
而现在 我就是时尚之母
In this one, I'm the mother of style.
我流的血都是迪奥的
Cut me and I bleed Dior.
你不是非要死的
And you don't have to be dead, you know.
所以你决定躲在你的安乐窝
So you decided to hole up in your happy place,
就像亿万富豪霍华德・休斯那样无忧无虑
like Howard Hughes without the crazy.
我们可以做到的
We can do this!
踩着一双五英寸的古驰
Stepping into the boardroom atop a pair
走进了会议室
of five-inch Guccis, well,
能让人领略到这一行的权威
that teaches the authority this business needed.
你要权衡你的框架 每一步都要考虑周全
You have to balance your frame, consider each step,
注入你所有的动力
and lean into your momentum.
最终你将得以升华
You wind up elevated.
大家好 我是Liz Taylor
Gentlemen, I'm Liz Taylor.
Drake先生委任我于此
Mr. Drake has sent me here
来带领公司迈向未来
to lead this company into the future.
直到Drake先生他能够
Until Mr. Drake has the courtesy
亲自现身董事会为止是吧
to appear before this board himself...
副主席先生 我可以向你保证
Mr. Vice-Chairman, I can assure you that Will Drake
Will Drake授予我全权来代表他行事
has granted me full authority to act on his behalf.
我不接受
I don't accept your authority.
我恐怕你不得不接受
I'm afraid you'll have to.
我已在Cortez酒店与Will Drake会过面了
I've met with Will Drake at the Hotel Cortez,
的确是正式的
and it's official.
Taylor女士在这里有全权
Ms. Taylor here has total authority
可以代表他发言
to speak on his behalf.
你被解雇了
You're fired.
大家注意了 关于重生 我很了解
Now, gentlemen, I know something about rebirth.
好好听 好好学
Listen and learn.
不行 我做不到
No! I can't do this!
这里四周都弥漫着灵感
There's inspiration all around us.
你所要做的就是去用心看
All you got to do is look.
我留下Will独自一人研究
I left Will alone to work his sorcery,
我去做我该做的事情
and he left me to mine.
# 白纱之夜 #
Nights in white satin...
我们让他的缺席变成一种神秘感
We cast his absence as mystery.
他很少在公开场合露面
He gave very little of himself to the public,
业绩需求却开始稳步上升
and demand steadily rose.
他的演出别具一格 独有一番情调
His presentations were exclusive and exotic.
并不会邀请太多人 所用模特也是非比寻常的
Very few invitations, very unusual models.
所有的相机和手机都会被禁止使用
All cameras and phones were banned,
这么做会让口碑越来越好
which only made word of mouth stronger,
更加吸引大家的热情
interest more intense.
装饰派艺术再次风靡起来
Art deco once again became all the rage.
# 我时常错过的美丽 #
Beauty I'd always missed
# 在他们眼前 #
With these eyes before
# 真相是什么 #
Just what the truth is...
我本该为我们大获成功而欢呼雀跃
I should've been jubilant in our success.
但恰恰相反 我很迷惑
But instead, I felt lost.
# 因为我爱你 #
'Cause I love you
# 我真的爱你 #
Yes, I love you...
我初遇Tristan的那一刻就像今晚这样
It was a night like this when I first saw Tristan.
答应我 你会保持这样开拓性的思维
Just promise me you'll keep an open mind.
拜托 也不看看我是谁
Please, remember to whom you speak.
我们现在在这里做什么
Now, what are we doing here?
我知道你有多想念Tristan
I know how much you miss Tristan.
无论他在哪 我也不知道为什么
And wherever he is, I don't know
我们连他的影子都没有看见过
why we haven't seen hide nor hair of him.
如果说有人能够联系到他的话
And if anybody can reach him,
那就只有这个女人了
this woman can.
Iris
Iris...
你为我找了个灵媒吗
did you get me a psychic?
Billie Dean Howard 这是Liz
Billie Dean Howard, this is Liz.
Liz 很高兴认识你
Liz, it is so good to meet you.
我看过公交车上有贴你的广告
I've seen you on the side of a bus.
Billie Dean在Lifetime电台有自己的节目
Billie Dean has her own show on Lifetime.
她帮助那些失去亲人的人们
She helps the bereaved communicate with
与他们深爱的人们进行沟通
their dearly departed loved ones.
我印象很深刻的
I'm impressed.
我如实说
I'll be honest.
在鬼屋界之中
Your establishment is fairly notorious
你们这里可真是大热门啊
among the paranormal communities being a bit of a hot spot.
我刚在想 我可能
I was thinking I might want
想要在这里录一集节目
to do an episode of my show here.
但不是今天
But today,
今天我是为你而来
I am here for you.
好多声音
Hmm, so many voices.
你们旅馆很吵闹啊
It's a very noisy hotel.
我感觉到了
Oh, I feel something.
一股充满男人的能量
A very masculine energy.
躁动不安
Restless.
他就在这里
He's here.
鬼魂啊
Spirit,
我们敞开心扉 真心实意寻找你
we seek you with loving hearts and open minds.
揭开将你我与世隔绝的面纱
Lift the veil that separates our world from yours.
向我们倾诉吧
Speak to us.
Tristan
Tristan.
你好
Hello.
Tristan 我现在和Liz站在一起
Tristan, I'm here with Liz.
她对你甚是想念
She misses you very much.
你有什么话想要对她说吗
Is there any message you have for her?
什么
What?
他说什么
What does he say?
他说
He says...
"没有"
"No."
你说"没有"是什么意思
What do you mean, "No"?
什么意思
What-what no?
他并不想说话
He doesn't want to talk.
什么意思 他刚刚跟你说话了
What do you mean? He's talking to you.
他是不想
He doesn't want to talk
跟我说
to me.
他一直在这里
He's been here all along.
而且他选择不跟我说话
And he's choosing not to talk to me...
因为他怪我
'cause he blames me.
我导致了他的死亡
I'm the cause of his death.
我对他的爱杀死了他
My love for him killed him.
爱不会死人
Love doesn't kill.
我活得时间更长 让我告诉你
I've been around a lot longer, and let me tell you something.
相信我 因爱而死的人比恨更多
Believe me, love kills a lot more than hate.
不管怎样 感谢你能来
Thank you for coming anyway.
坚强点
Be strong.
我知道你懂的
I know you know how.
是啊
Yep.
不 不是这样的
No. This isn't right.
不 等等
No, wait.
也许跟你说话的不是Tristan
Maybe it wasn't Tristan you were talking to.
他记得那馅饼
He remembers the pancakes.
蓝莓馅的
The ones with the blueberries.
你每周六做给他吃
You made them for him every Saturday
让他看一上午动画片
and let him watch cartoons all morning.
谁是Donovan
Who's Donovan?
怎么了
What?
Donovan不在这里
Donovan isn't here.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
Donovan在别的地方
Donovan is someplace else.
在某个仙境
Someplace very beautiful.
他说那里闻起来像馅饼
He says it smells like pancakes.
你做的馅饼
Your pancakes.
他说他总是周六的早上在那里
He says it's always Saturday morning where he is.
他说
He says...
我爱你 妈妈
"I love you, Mom."
即使我很难过 我依然为我的朋友感到高兴
Even in my grief, I was happy for my friend.
至于我 我感受爱的机会已经没了
As for me, I felt any chance at love was over.
但是生命总会给你惊喜
But life can surprise you.
特别是新的生命
Especially new life.
以及爱
And love?
这可能有很多方式
Well, that can take many forms.
在我和我的儿子Douglas和好后
After I made peace with my son Douglas,
我真的从未想过会再见到他
I never really expected to see him again.
所以当他带Janice来见我时我很开心
So I was delighted when he brought Janice to meet me.
我一直想要Janice这样的儿媳妇
Janice was the daughter I always wanted.
而且我也是她一直想要的婆婆
And I was the mother-in-law she'd always hoped for.
在Isabelle的脸上 我看到了未来
In Isabelle's face, I saw the future.
她出生的年代比我出生那时候
She was being born into a world just a little more accepting
更加包容
than the one I had been born into.
可能 只是可能
And maybe, just maybe,
我可以为此做点什么
I had a little something to do with that.
一点善意和认可
A little kindness, acceptance.
除此之外没什么能改变我
That transformed me in ways nothing else ever could.
我从未想过人生会这么好
I never thought life could be this good.
以及生命可能会这样结束
Or that it might end.
该死
Well, shit!
你确定
Are you sure?
是的
I'm sure.
医生确诊了
the doctor is sure.
他们不能做点什么吗
And there ain't nothing they can do about it?
过了治疗的时机了
It's... past the point of treatment.
这可能是最好的结果
Which is probably for the best.
因为
'Cause...
我可能会讨厌失去我的头发
I would hate to lose my hair.
乖乖
Baby girl,
我可能能为你做点什么
there just might be something that I can do for you.
什么 转变我
What, turn me?
老天 我甚至都不喜欢带血的牛排
Hell, I don't even like my steak bloody.
但我从没想过这样做
But that's never been an option for me.
你知道的
You know that.
在我人生中的这个时刻
And at this point in my life,
我不敢想象为了生存去杀戮
I can't imagine killing in order to live.
你跟你的孩子说了没
So have you told your kids yet?
运气好的话 我就不用说了
With any luck, I won't need to.
他们可以一直到这里来看我
They can just keep visiting me here.
我就不废话了
I'm gonna cut to the chase.
我是世界上第一个患有前列腺癌的女人
I am the first woman in the world to have prostate cancer.
医生告诉我已经扩散到脊椎了
Uh, the doctor told me it's spread to the spine
已经没治了
and there's nothing to do.
我们会不惜一切代价
We'll spend whatever we have to.
一个电话我就能为你联系到世界上最好的医生
One call and I can get you to the best doctor in the world.
太晚了
Oh, it's too late.
我不想在医院
And I don't want to spend
挂着个尿袋 不断的打针吃药
my last days wasting away in a hospital
浪费我最后的日子
with a catheter up my dick and poison in my body,
所以
so...
但谁会来照顾我们
But who will take care of us?
- 你不能丢下我们 - 我不会的
You can't leave us alone. I won't.
这就是我今天把你们都叫过来的原因
That's why I called you all here today.
现在 我给你们提供了各种武器
Now, I have provided you with various weapons.
挑两个吧 它们很小
Take two. They're small.
砍我
hack me.
勒我
Strangle me.
重击我
Bludgeon me.
给我惊喜
Surprise me.
我想我能代表这里的每个人去说
I think I can speak for everyone here when I say
我们全都开始变得喜欢你了
that we've all grown rather fond of you.
我们不可能杀你的
We can't possibly murder you.
这不是谋杀
It's not murder.
她想要重生
She wants to be reborn.
你们是我的家人
You're my family.
我想要永远和你们在一起
I want to be with you forever.
这是她死后的第一次我见到她
It was the first time I'd seen her since she died.
直到那一刻我才意识到
Only in that moment did I realize
我有多想她
just how much I'd missed her.
你怎么出现了
How did you know to come?
你一直是我最爱的作品
You were always my fondest creation.
我想在这里帮你转生
I wanted to be here to help you transition.
最后一次
One last time.
这东西会害死你的
Those things'll kill you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你都不跟我说话
You wouldn't talk to me.
我以为你恨我
I thought you hated me.
我爱你
I love you.
亲爱的
And, darlin',
你要活得更久
you had more living to do.
我不能这样妨碍你
I couldn't get in the way of that.
宝贝
Oh, baby...
你太好了
you are to die for.
- 有什么需要吗 - 我有个预约
- May I help you? - I have a reservation.
44号房
Room 44.
求爱屋
The Woo room.
Billie Dean说那是他死的地方
That's where Billie Dean says he died.
那间被预定了
Oh, that room is booked.
被我订了 三星期前
Booked by me, three weeks ago.
以Ashley Rhodes名义
Under Rhodes, Ashley.
我的软件上显示款已付请
My Amex app says the charge has cleared.
你收了我的钱 我要我的房间
You have my money. I want my room.
好吧
Fine.
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
我以为Billie会是免费的广告
I thought that Billie'd be free advertising.
人们爱极了好的鬼故事
You know, people love a good ghost story.
你说的没错
Well, you were right about that.
是啊 但这失控了
Yeah, but this is getting way out of hand.
她已有三个黄金特刊了
She's had three prime-time specials.
等一下 等一下
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等 他在试着告诉我什么
Wait, he's trying to tell me something.
Woo先生没付什么钱
Mr. Woo doesn't pay for what?
我是说 别误解了我的意思
I mean, don't get me wrong.
我不介意这个地方挤满了各种客人
I don't mind having this place alive with guests.
只是那些希望被鬼魂蹂躏的
It's just those freaks and weirdos
奇奇怪怪的家伙
who want to be plowed by a ghost.
Billie吸引来的人 他们会...
The people Billie attracts, they're just...
对我们的品牌不好的
It's bad for our brand.
我们为什么不关掉这个地方呢
Why don't we just shut the place down?
Will Drake不再需要钱了
Will Drake doesn't need the money anymore.
因为这个地方需要生命
'Cause this place needs life.
这是个旅馆 不是个墓地
It's a hotel, not a cemetery.
生者给困在这里的灵魂
The living give the spirits trapped in this place
一个与外界世界的链接
a connection to the outside world.
John
John.
我还在想你什么时候会来呢
I was wondering when you were gonna arrive.
我们好想你
We've missed you.
回来的感觉真好 你是对的
It's good to be back. And you're right.
我不喜欢她来拜访
I don't like her coming around.
不断打扰 问各种问题
Pestering, asking questions.
她还在尝试联系我吗
She still trying to contact me?
每一年这个日子都会
Every year on this date.
John Lowe
John Lowe.
十诫杀手
The Ten Commandments Killer.
现身来证明你的罪恶吧
Show yourself and bear witness to your crimes.
该死的
Shit.
打电话给她
Call her.
让她入住我的房间
Check her into my room.
但是要尽快带她来
But get her here quickly.
还有三小时就要日落了
It's only three hours until sundown.
我们现在在Cortez旅馆的64号房
We are standing in room 64 of the Hotel Cortez,
这是臭名昭著的十诫杀手许多年前
where the notorious Ten Commandments Killer lived
在洛杉矶实施恐怖统治时住过的地方
when he terrorized Los Angeles many years ago.
John Lowe可能是我所尝试联系的
John Lowe may be the most evil and dangerous spirit
最邪恶也最危险的灵魂
with whom I have ever attempted to make contact.
我需要集中我所有的技术和能量
I will need all of my skills and powers of concentration
来达成这次史无前例的采访
to achieve this unprecedented interview.
你想谈谈吗
You wanted to talk?
我想让你来谈谈
I want you to talk.
我的名字是Billie Dean Howard
My name is Billie Dean Howard.
我们所知道的关于John Lowe的事都是警察那儿得来的
All we know about John Lowe is what the police have said.
我现在给你一个机会来为自己陈述
I'm giving you a chance now to set the record straight.
你想要知道什么
What do you want to know?
我们就从你的家庭开始吧
Why don't we start with your family.
他们知道
Did they know
你是一个杀人恶魔吗
you were a serial killer?
- 你给Holden准备了什么晚餐 - 还是狗肉
- What'd you get Holden for dinner? - It's dog again.
他们慢慢理解了
They came to understand
我是在用我自己的方式
that I was cleaning up the world,
- 净化这个世界 - 该死的 John
- in my own way. - Goddamn it, John.
我们谈过这个 我的目标都是
We talked about this; I was not gonna target people
那些该死的人
who do not deserve to die.
现在 你一旦潜逃了
Now, once you went on the lam,
你就再也见不到你的妻子和两个孩子了
your wife and two children were never seen again.
快点
Come on.
- 你要去哪儿 - 他饿了
- Where are you going? - He's hungry.
我知道怎样不被察觉的
I know how to walk into a hospital
走去医院
and not get noticed.
你杀了他们吗
Did you kill them?
我会承认 我对不起他们
I will admit, I failed them.
爸爸
Daddy?
只剩一件事情要做了
There's only one thing left to do.
自首吗
Turn myself in?
我们必须得回家
We have to go home.
Scarlett是对的
Scarlett was right.
科尔特斯[科罗拉多州]是家
The Cortez was home.
我们以某种方式 在那里重生
We'd all been reborn there, in one form or another.
除了她以外
Well, except for her.
我们的女儿仍有机会
There was a still a chance for our daughter
在别的地方长大
to grow up somewhere else,
有机会过平凡的生活
to have some shot at a normal life.
但是这需要远离我们
But it needed to be away from us.
Liz正好知道一个地方
Liz knew just the place.
撒切尔学校会接收很多
The Thatcher School would be host
科尔特斯旅馆避难的年轻人
to more than one young refugee from the Hotel Cortez.
所以你把你女儿送走了
So you sent your daughter away,
但是跟你的妻子和儿子一起生活在斯尔特斯
but lived with your son and wife in the Cortez,
回到仍在追捕你的洛杉矶
back in L.A., where you were still being hunted.
当你在逃亡的时候很难顾及家庭
It's hard to provide for your family when you're on the run.
在洛杉矶会有更多的机会
There were more opportunities in Los Angeles.
站住 John Lowe 你被捕了
Stop! John Lowe, you're under arrest!
我必须要回到旅馆
I have to make it back to the hotel.
让我...
Let me...
我要死在里面
I want to die inside.
我能感觉到你的妻子和儿子
I'm sensing something about your wife and son.
我能听到灵魂的暗流
I can hear the undercurrents from the spirits,
但是他们太惊恐了说不清楚话
but they are too afraid to speak clearly.
为什么会这样
Why is that?
我不想谈论我的家庭
I don't want to talk about my family.
好啊 如果你不想再说关于家庭的事
Well, if you don't want to talk about your family,
那么告诉我点别的
then give me something else.
十月三十日为什么那么重要
What is the significance of October 30?
为什么那是我唯一感受到你现身在这儿的日子
Why is it the only day I feel your presence here?
这是属于恶魔的夜晚
Well, it's Devil's Night.
如果你把你的摄制组留在这儿
And if you leave your camera crew behind,
我就能展示给你看
that I can show you.
他们在尖叫
They're screaming.
我曾经在西边的一栋房子里
I was in a house once just west of here.
我能听到墙里的灵魂 像是白蚁...
And I could hear the spirits in the walls like termites...
或是阁楼上的老鼠
or bats in the attic.
但从没见过现在这样
But it was nothing like this.
这像是在亡者的摇滚音乐会中一样
This is like being in a rock concert of the dead.
来吧
Well, come on.
让我引荐给你亡者的摇滚明星
Let me introduce you to some rock stars of the dead.
噢 Jeffrey 你和你该死的吸管
Oh, Jeffrey, you and your damn straws.
快来 放下你的饮料来跟我跳舞吧
Come on. Put your drink down and come and dance with me.
我不跳舞
I don't dance.
看着我
Look at me.
我也不跳
Neither do I.
John 噢
John! Oh!
Jeffrey 看看是谁来了
Jeffrey, look who's here.
John来了
John is here.
他是他们里面最棒的
He's the greatest of them all.
你在脸红吗
Are you blushing?
我告诉过你 如果你喜欢一个人 你必须要跟他讲话
I told you, if you like a guy, you have to talk to him.
你觉得如果我没有胆子接近他们&
You think any of those young men
这些年轻人
would have come over to work at my house if I didn't have
真的会来我的屋子工作吗
the guts to approach them in the world?
这些密尔沃基的家伙一定极度渴望
Well, those guys in Milwaukee must have been pretty desperate
跟着Jeffrey回家的
to go home with Jeffrey.
这个男孩说两个字就会脸红的
The guy can't get two words out without going flush.
噢 天呐
Oh, my God.
你是John Wayne Gacy
You're John Wayne Gacy.
那是Jeffrey Dahmer
And that's Jeffrey Dahmer.
你被吓到了吗
Are you frightened?
没有
Oh, no.
我只是让纯洁的灵魂围绕在我周围
No, I just surround myself with the white light of spirit and...
来保护我自己
to keep myself protected.
当然 小甜心
Sure thing, sweetheart.
耶 我们开始派对吧
Yeah! Let's get this party started!
我需要啤酒 要随便什么冷的东西
I need a beer. I'll drink whatever's cold.
我去 这狗屁音乐是什么鬼
Jesus H. Christ on a horse, what the hell is this shit music?
Aileen Wuornos
Aileen Wuornos.
Richard Ramirez
Richard Ramirez.
我结婚了 但是我们分居
I'm married, but we live apart.
这是Zodiac
And that's the Zodiac.
我去给你拿点喝的
I'll get you a drink.
# 我想要牵着你的手 #
# I want to hold the hand inside you #
嗨
Uh, hey.
我是Aileen
I'm Aileen.
# 我想要深呼吸... #
# I want to take a breath... #
你拥有最美的头发
You have the prettiest hair.
噢 为这样的一头秀发我什么都可以做
Man, what I wouldn't do for a head of hair like that.
就像... 就像Farrah Fawcett
It's like... it's like Farrah Fawcett.
让我想起了我的前女友
Reminds me of my... my ex-girlfriend.
我很不舒服
Oh, I feel ill.
这些黑暗的灵魂
All these dark spirits.
有点... 太汹涌了
It's... it's a little overwhelming.
把它喝了 它会使你放松的
Just drink that. It'll relax you.
字幕
Absinthe!
Our customary libation.
字幕
James Patrick March.
Oh.
字幕
Oh, I feel the violence in you.
So many spirits who you snuffed out.
字幕
I can see all the moments when they crossed over.
Tell me,
字幕
what is that like?
Is it a moving picture, like so many cells on a film reel?
字幕
Or more like a kaleidoscope of human suffering?
It's not a picture.
字幕
It's a feeling.
Like a mist on your face on a cold morning.
字幕
You can't see it in the air, but you can feel...
the wetness.
字幕
Yeah. I can feel the wetness
with you so close to me right now, Johnny boy.
字幕
I got a seat right next to me.
So this is Devil's Night.
字幕
My Murderers' Row!
How odd it must be to see all of us then
字幕
in what appears to be the flesh.
Flesh enough to eat,
字幕
drink,
feel our grip on your arm,
字幕
our breath on your skin.
No!
字幕
How's that white light holding up, Billie Dean?
I don't want to be here anymore.
字幕
When does the party favor arrive?
John's taken care of that.
字幕
Grab your weapons,
ladies and gents.
字幕
No.
Can't throw a killer party without a little killing, right?
字幕
Don't worry, Billie.
I think you're gonna like living here.
字幕
Here's the deal.
No more specials or interviews
字幕
or books or tweets or casual conversations
at cocktail parties with Shirley MacLaine
字幕
about this hotel.
This place is dead to you.
字幕
We will become a myth,
which is what we should've been left to do anyway.
字幕
What if I don't?
One sure-as-shit thing I can tell you
字幕
about being murdered: it hurts.
And we like to make it last...
字幕
None of you can leave the hotel, so...
you can't hold me to my word, huh?
字幕
But I can.
What the hell are you?
字幕
You're not dead.
I'm a creature
字幕
who kills to live
and who drinks a body's worth of blood a day
字幕
and doesn't think twice about
who I'm sucking it from.
字幕
So, if you even let out a whisper of a word
that sounds like "Cortez,"
字幕
I'll find you and drain every drop of life
from your skinny ass.
字幕
I can't be the only one here
hoping you say no.
字幕
No!
No! No!
字幕
Did you take care of what you had to take care of?
Yeah.
字幕
Look at you, Scarlett.
Where'd my little girl go?
字幕
You're just saying that 'cause
I'm the only member of the family that ages.
字幕
Thanks for coming.
Tonight means a lot to me.
字幕
For us
all to be together.
字幕
Even just for a few hours.
Of course, Dad.
字幕
Means a lot to me, too.
Go on.
字幕
Get into bed with them.
Not you?
字幕
I'm getting a little big
for the family bed.
字幕
I'll take the chair.
I'm afraid to fall asleep.
字幕
As soon as I close my eyes,
it'll all be gone for another year.
字幕
It's okay, Daddy.
Rest.
字幕
What brings you to the Cortez?
Tomorrow's Halloween.
字幕
This place is supposed to be haunted, right?
I'm meeting some friends here.
字幕
No, you're not.
I'm not?
字幕
No.
You have a jawline for days.